(Episode 13)
Drink this.
Jun Seo.
Do you really need to go to the U.S.?
Can you live with me...
just for six months?
Just for six months...
I'm not asking for any more,
just six months.
Could you do that?
Eun Seo.
What's going on with you?
Can't you live with me?
Can't you?
It is...
too late now.
What are you talking about?
What is too late?
You'll live with Yu Mi
for the rest of your life.
Why can't you live with me for six months?
Eun Seo.
Why are you doing this?
Can't I ask you for this?
Can't I do that?
I like you.
I like you a lot.
But why do I have to give you up?
Why do I have to put up with it?
Why am I the only one?
Do you want to live with me,
letting Yu Mi give up on her life?
Can you do that?
Can you?
No.
No, I can't.
Eun Seo.
This is the only thing...
I can do now.
We're seeing each other twice today.
Would you like water?
Why don't we have something strong?
Did something happen to Eun Seo?
What's going on with her?
Nothing's going on. Did you meet Eun Seo?
She came to meet me.
Are you sure nothing's happened to her?
Are you sure?
I don't think you can ask me about her.
Do you think you can?
Do you think you have the right to ask?
I'm taking care of her now.
You needn't get bothered about it.
Hello.
Yes.
Yes, this is Han Tae Seok who asked.
(Cancer Can Be Beaten,
Road to the Complete Cure)
What?
Did she faint?
I'm sorry. I need to go now.
What's going on? Who fainted?
A friend. You don't need to know.
(Emergency Medical Center)
How are you feeling?
Doctor.
Please save me, doctor.
Save me.
I am scared, doctor. I am scared.
Please save me.
Can you live with me...
just for six months?
Jun Seo, I'm back.
Jun Seo?
Jun Seo.
Yu Mi.
Could you give me some time?
Just a few months...
If I ask that I do whatever I like
for a few months...
and promise to come back to you,
could you...
allow me to do that?
Go.
Go away.
Go away, not for a few months,
but forever.
Just go away.
What's the point of all this?
What's the point?
Yu Mi.
Do you take me for a fool?
Am I a fool?
Why are you making me so miserable?
If you'd like to keep doing this, just go.
Go away.
Don't leave.
Why is it so difficult to make it?
Are you feeling better?
How are you feeling? Are you in any pain?
I'm sorry I scared you.
I'm leaving now.
I found the hospital.
They want you to be admitted immediately.
I have sent them
your medical records already.
Tae Seok.
Listen.
Listen to me.
We can beat this.
It's just difficult to cure.
I heard it's not necessarily
a fatal disease.
The hospital I found...
has a lake nearby,
and the scenery is also beautiful.
Also, it's the best hospital
for treating cancer in Korea.
If they can't fix you,
I'll take you to any hospital that can.
I'll do my best to save you.
I will.
I know you're thinking about giving up.
You're about to give up.
Eun Seo.
Do you want me to tell Jun Seo?
Should I tell him?
Should I let Jun Seo know you're sick?
Please don't tell him.
Don't, Tae Seok.
He's leaving for the U.S. soon,
so he doesn't need to know.
He shouldn't know it.
He should never know it.
I'm sorry, Tae Seok.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be so mean to you like this.
Don't be sorry.
You don't need to be sorry, Eun Seo.
So, please go to the hospital with me.
Since you've been mean to me until now,
you should give me a chance at least.
What if I can't do anything...
and you die?
What should I do?
If I'm aware that you're sick
yet can't do anything,
how could I live with myself?
It's not for you. It's for me.
Please go to the hospital for me.
Don't you think...
you should do it for me at least?
Think about what you've done to me.
Do you really want to die?
Are you going to die?
I want to live.
Eun Seo,
what are you doing?
I'm just polishing dishes.
I know you don't have time for this.
Leave it.
It's always been your job.
What's so special about it this time?
Right, I always do this,
so I'll polish all the dishes
while I have the time.
By the way,
- Mom.
- Yes?
I found a job.
Did you?
I got hired at a big hotel in Seoul.
Isn't that great?
Also, these are your socks,
and these are your lingerie.
And...
this.
Do you like it?
Take it away. Are you out of your mind?
What is all this?
I don't need any of that.
Also, what is this lingerie for?
It's more than enough
to wear for the rest of my life.
It'll be nice if you could wear them
for the rest of your life.
I just bought you some you can wear
for the rest of your life, didn't I?
Are you not coming back
once you go to Seoul?
Mom, look at this. Isn't it pretty?
Try it on.
What's wrong with you?
- No.
- Come on, Mom.
You look great.
My mom is beautiful.
I believe I look like you.
It was my wish to get you
a beautiful winter jacket.
Do you feel sorry for me?
No, I feel grateful for you.
Mom, thank you so much.
I want to give you only the best things.
I'll show you my best.
Do you want to get off work with me?
You and Jun Seo just turned
the whole family upside down.
How shameless you are.
I'm sorry.
I can't since I'm on duty tonight.
Sin Ae.
I came here to ask you a favor.
A favor? To me?
I'm going to Seoul.
I'm going to work in Seoul.
I won't come back for a long time.
Mom.
My mom.
Please look after her.
I have no one to ask but you.
You know how Jong Chul is.
I have only you to ask this.
Please come by her once in a while
after I'm gone.
Mom has only you besides me.
Do you have anything else to say?
As for your mom...
I won't see her often anymore.
So, I want to sleep over
at your house tonight.
Can you let me do that, just for today?
You're being ridiculous.
Why are you acting like
you're dying or something?
Am I?
Sin Ae.
Please.
Why do I have to look after your mom?
Bye.
I don't want to see you ever again.
Mom.
You hate me, don't you?
What are you talking about?
How can I hate you, Eun Seo?
Whenever I think of you,
it makes me so happy.
Is that true?
Of course.
I'm sorry, Mom.
It would've been better if I hadn't been
your daughter from the beginning.
No, it wouldn't.
It wouldn't.
I'm so happy I had you.
We were apart. We had our hearts broken,
and it's been hard for us
because of you and Jun Seo.
But compared to the happiness
you brought me,
all those things are nothing.
When you were little,
you plucked a flower for me
for the first time.
It was a breathtaking moment.
The flower was crushed in your tiny hand,
but you walked to me as a toddler.
You have no idea how happy I was.
My daughter.
Mom.
Are you going to cry?
Why are you crying, silly?
Now it's like we're always together,
isn't it?
Right?
Dad and Mom, goodbye.
Jun Seo, goodbye.
Hello, Director, you're here.
You've been taking good care
of my sister, Eun Seo,
and found her a job in Seoul.
It's all right.
I might have favors to ask you later.
Can you get your blood tested
at this hospital?
What? A blood test?
I don't have any disease.
It's not about that.
I'm asking you a favor.
Sure, you can ask me.
I'll do anything you ask me.
Hello.
I'm going to Seoul too, Ms. Soon Im.
I'll come by often to see how she is.
Mom.
Yes.
Call me as soon as you arrive.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Mom.
Yes.
I'll see you later.
Sure.
It's probably the last chance
since he leaves for the U.S. soon.
Don't you want to meet him,
even if you have to lie?
Did you meet him?
I don't want to say it,
but did you meet Jun Seo?
No.
Good.
Here you are.
Right.
Thanks for doing this every time.
These chestnuts look so tasty, don't they?
It's nothing.
I just shared what I got from the hotel.
Where is Jun Seo?
Jun Seo is...
I'll get him.
It seemed like something bad had happened.
He drank during the day.
Did Jun Seo drink during the daytime?
I know.
Isn't it odd?
Jun Seo. Yoon Jun Seo.
- You came.
- Did you drink again?
Manager Kim came.
What is wrong with you these days?
You've been holding up well,
but why are you like that these days?
Why are you drinking all the time?
Keep yourself together.
I'm sober. Let's go.
What? Did Eun Seo?
Didn't you know that?
I don't know about the details.
She said Director Han found her
a position at a hotel in Seoul.
She came to say goodbye yesterday
and said she was going to Seoul.
To Seoul?
Is Eun Seo going to Seoul?
Yes.
I thought you all knew it already.
Jun Seo, you are leaving for
the U.S. next month.
So I assumed she met you to say farewell.
That's why I just said it.
Jun Seo.
Yu Mi.
You are all here.
I came over to say "goodbye."
I'm going to Seoul today.
We need to talk.
Jun Seo.
We need to talk in private.
Go.
You could've just left.
Why did you come here?
I'm regretting it, too.
Don't be like that.
Jun Seo won't betray Shin Yu Mi
even if you don't do anything.
Are you blaming me?
Me? Blaming you?
Blaming whom?
Han Tae Seok. What a coward.
I can't even be honest with her
because I'm scared of losing her again.
Tae Seok.
Don't bother.
Don't blame yourself.
I'm way worse than you are.
If Jun Seo finds out the truth,
he might kill me.
What do you mean?
Why are you leaving?
I'm the one who should leave.
I know you're leaving.
I know that, but...
I was tired of waiting for you to leave.
I was tired of waiting.
Where are you going?
Where are you going in Seoul?
I'm not going to Seoul.
You're the only one who knows this.
I'm leaving with Tae Seok.
He asked me to run away with him.
He sounds like someone I know, isn't he?
- Eun Seo.
- I promised Tae Seok.
I'll live for him from now on.
But it can be hard to do that here.
We're going to start a new life together
somewhere else.
Are you...
going to live with Tae Seok?
I mean it.
I mean it, and so does he.
It was my mistake the other day.
I shouldn't have...
said that to you the other day.
That was my bad.
I'm really embarrassed.
So, you should think...
it was good of you
to say no to me that day.
Talking of that day,
thank you for saying "no."
I thought...
you knew how I felt.
I knew.
And I know how you feel.
But we both know...
that we can't be together.
Don't forget that I know how you feel.
I really do.
Your love for me will live in my heart.
So, I have no regrets or resentment.
You shouldn't forget that.
Don't forget I know everything
about how you feel.
Don't regret anything,
no matter what happens.
You shouldn't regret anything...
Okay?
Look at you.
What can I do if you look like
you regret it already?
I told you not to.
I should get going, then.
I'm regretting it.
I really am regretting it.
Lay on your left side, please.
Pull your knees to your belly.
It hurt, didn't it?
It did a little.
He should be around.
He was so anxious.
He looked much sicklier than you.
When did you come?
I just came.
You had your test today, didn't you?
Did it hurt?
A little.
It hurt just this much.
Did it?
I see.
What's wrong with this? It's unusual.
What's wrong with you?
You said you would take care of me.
I'm sorry.
Jun Seo, it's me.
You haven't forgotten about
the family gathering tonight, have you?
I'm in Seoul now, and will go straight
to your parents' home in Sokcho.
See you later.
Also, are you drinking now by any chance?
Please don't drink.
Is this where Shin Yu Mi is?
Yu Mi, it's Dr. Kim.
I told you to revisit to check,
but I don't think that's necessary.
Your test result shows
that your hand has completely healed.
Congratulations.
You should throw a party again
with your fiancé.
Jun Seo is getting late.
He'll be here soon.
Let's start eating without him.
But it's been a while
since we had a family gathering.
Right.
Are you worried, Yu Mi?
Don't worry.
He'll probably be here soon,
since he hasn't called.
He always calls when he's running late,
even if it's for ten minutes.
It should be him, Sin Ae.
I'll get it.
Are you drunk?
You smell like alcohol.
Jun Seo, get yourself together.
I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
I'm late.
Jun Seo.
What's wrong with you?
I am sorry, Mom.
I hung out with a friend...
Jun Seo, why are you so drunk?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Go away.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Are you okay, Jun Seo?
I am fine.
I'm all right.
I am sorry.
Mom, I am sorry.
I am sorry. What's wrong with me?
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, what's the matter?
It's broken.
Mom, I'll get another one.
Jun Seo.
Hello.
Yes, Doctor.
A message? No, I haven't.
Okay, thank you.
Yes.
Jun Seo.
You knew.
You knew my hand got healed.
I'm sorry.
I was going to tell you,
but I didn't want you to know.
I thought that if my hand got better,
you would leave me.
That's why I lied.
I didn't want to lose you,
even if I had to lie.
That's great news,
and you should've told me that earlier.
Jun Seo.
I mean it.
You can paint again.
I am very happy for you.
I really...
wanted to have you for myself,
even if I had to lie.
I wished my hand wouldn't get better.
I know.
I get it.
I understand.
Then, don't leave.
Don't go to Eun Seo.
I'm not going to Eun Seo.
No, I won't go to her.
That won't happen.
I just want to travel for a few days.
Will you let me?
Will you forgive me?
Forgive you?
I should be the one
asking for forgiveness.
I'm sorry for not getting myself together.
I'm sorry for making you worried.
Eun Seo moved on when she was
leaving these mugs behind.
She has moved on,
but I was a fool, not being able to do it.
I'll be back after clearing my head.
Just give me a couple of days.
Then we will go to the U.S.
While I'm gone,
can you keep these mugs?
When I'm back,
these will be nothing more than mugs.
Choi Eun Seo, are you scared?
Ms. Choi.
Do you know how painful it is?
It hurts a lot.
But do I have to do the test again?
You did well last time.
Why are you scared?
You said it's nothing.
Then you should try it yourself this time.
No, why do I do that?
I wish I could.
Must I go through this painful test?
Even if it hurts,
there's no guarantee I will get better.
Why do I need to do this?
Do that for me.
I know what I said is not going to work.
Why are you saying that?
You don't like me.
Tae Seok.
Could you get me a lucky charm?
The necklace.
Can I get it back?
I'll hold it whenever I feel pain.
I will have that as my lucky charm.
Can I do that?
Yes, you can.
You can have it.
That wouldn't be a big deal.
But can I give you something else,
instead of the necklace?
Please come to the injection room.
Jun Seo.